Guide to the Mike Cox Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2018-111
  - "Center Point Cemetery 8/17; Frontier Times, Newsclippings, Programs, Napkin, Correspondence, Burial Info, 1924-1999 (Box 2870, Folder 27)
  - "Chronology, Texas Rangers"; Texas Ranger Dispatch, Texas Ranger Timeline, 1999-2001 (Box 2870, Folder 28)
  - "Coffees in Rangers"; Who Was Ranger Coffee, Southwestern Quarterly, Phonebook Info, True West, 1953-1990 (Box 2870, Folder 29)
  - "Neal, Caldwell"; Frontier Times, January 1948 (Box 2870, Folder 30)
  - "Collectibles, Ranger"; Texas Ranger Trading Cards, Commemorative Gun Order Forms, The Fan Man, Order Forms, Magazines, and News clippings, 1967-1998 (Box 2870, Folder 31)
  - "Ft. Colorado"; News clippings, Photographs, Short Stories, Notes, Correspondence, 1962-1981 (Box 2870, Folder 32)
  - "Colonial Texas Rangers"; Articles, News clippings, Quarterly Journals, Printed Biographies, 1918-1992 (Box 2870, Folder 33)
  - "Connor, Buck"; Adjutant General Department, Oath of Members Ranger Force, Biography, and News Article, 1887-1916 (Box 2870, Folder 34)
  - "Cook, Thalis T."; The Steer Branded Murder, Frontier Times, Voice of the Mexican Border, Articles, and Notes, 1889-1999 (Box 2870, Folder 35)
  - "Scott Cooley"; Scott Cooley – A Byword for Terror, April 2003 (Box 2870, Folder 36)